so as you may already know you can
所以你可能已经知道你可以
change the colors of objects in inkscape
更改Inkscape中对象的颜色
by clicking on them one by one and
通过一个接一个地点击它们
applying fill colors
应用填充颜色
but what if you wanted to change an
但是，如果您想要更改
entire range of colors all at once so
所有的颜色都会同时出现，所以
that you get a more consistent result
你会得到一个更一致的结果
like this while saving yourself a bunch
就像这样，还能省下一大笔钱
of time
时间的流逝
this is where the hsl adjustment
这就是HSL调整的地方
extension comes in handy and in this
扩展使用起来很方便，而且在这里
tutorial we'll be going over how you can
教程，我们将介绍您如何
use it
用它吧
so to get started I have this example
因此，作为开始，我有这个例子
design here on my canvas it just
在我的画布上设计它只是
consists of individual Vector objects
由单个矢量对象组成
I'm going to click and drag over all of
我要单击并拖动所有
them to select them and group it all
以选择它们并将其全部分组
together by going to object and
一起去反对和
selecting group
选择组
now I'm going to open up my extensions
现在我要打开我的分机
menu over here I'll come down to where
菜单在这里，我要到哪里去
it says color and I will select hsl
上面写着颜色，我会选择HSL
adjust
调整
let me bring this menu over here now hsl
现在让我把菜单拿过来，HSL
stands for Hue saturation and lightness
代表色调饱和度和明度
to show you how this works let me turn
为了向你展示这是如何工作的，让我转身
on the live preview
在现场预展上
first I'll show you what saturation and
首先，我将向您展示什么是饱和度和
lightness does and then I will explain
轻装上阵，然后我会解释
you so saturation is the intensity of
你如此饱和是一种强烈的
the color so if I bring this all the way
颜色，所以如果我一直带着这个
up we have more vibrant intense colors
在上面我们有更鲜艳的强烈颜色
if I bring this all the way down
如果我把这个一直带下去
the colors become more muted and if I
颜色变得更加柔和，如果我
bring it all the way down like that we
把它一直带下去，就像我们
end up with an almost or a black and
以几乎或黑色结束，然后
white image as you can see there in that
你可以在里面看到白色的图像
grayscale
灰度级
let me set this back to zero
让我把这个调回零
lightness represents the lightness of
明度代表了
the color so if I bring this up we end
所以如果我提起这件事我们就结束了
up with the lighter result like that or
带着这样轻松的结果，还是
if I bring this down we end up with a
如果我把这件事搞砸了，我们就会得到一个
darker result like that
像这样更黑暗的结果
so let me reset that as well
所以让我也重新设置一下
and then finally Hue is what you would
最后，色调就是你想要的
use to change the actual color so if I
用于更改实际颜色，因此如果我
move this over here
把这个搬到这里来
we end up with this color or if I move
我们以这个颜色结束，或者如果我移动
this down more we end up with that color
这个再往下一点，我们就会得到那个颜色
and as you go up and down this scale
当你在这个标尺上上下移动时
here you can run through the entire
在这里，您可以运行整个
gamut the entire range of colors you can
尽你所能地将所有颜色色域色域
make this object virtually any color
将此对象设置为几乎任何颜色
that you want you can use green blue or
你想要的，你可以用绿色、蓝色或
whatever and the thumbnail of the video
和视频的缩略图
I used a pinkish purple so I will use
我用的是粉紫色，所以我会用
something like that right there and then
像这样的东西就在那里然后
you can if you want to you can change
你可以，如果你想，你可以改变
the saturation to increase the the
饱和度，以增加
intensity of that color
该颜色的强度
and then finally over here you can use
然后最后在这里，你可以使用
your lightness to adjust that if you
你的轻盈来调整它如果你
want I think this looks better
想要吗？我觉得这个看起来更好。
with a modest lightness like that and
像这样适度的轻盈，
once you're finished click the apply
完成后，请单击应用
button once and I say once because once
按钮一次，我说一次，因为一次
you click it nothing visibly is going to
你点击它，看不到任何东西会
happen on your screen well nothing
在你的屏幕上发生什么都没发生
nothing's going to change that you can
没有什么能改变你能做的事
see anyway but the changes are now
不管怎么说，这些变化现在已经发生了
applied and if you click that button
已应用，如果您单击该按钮
again it's going to apply those changes
同样，它将应用这些更改
a second time so you'll end up with a
第二次，这样你就会得到一个
different result so that's one thing to
不同的结果，所以这是一回事
keep in mind click that button once and
请记住，只需点击一次按钮即可
once you click it close out of the menu
一旦你点击它，关闭菜单
and now if I ungroup these objects and
现在，如果我将这些对象解组并
select them one by one you can see their
一个接一个地选择你可以看到他们的
colors have indeed been changed this is
颜色确实变了，这是
not a temporary filter or some kind of
不是临时过滤器或某种
adjustment layer these are actual
调整层这些都是实际的
changes that have been applied to the
已应用于
subject as you can see there
正如你在那里看到的主题
so that is how you can change colors
这就是你可以改变颜色的方式
globally using the hsl adjustment in
全局使用中的HSL调整
inkscape if you found this lesson useful
Inkscape如果你觉得这一课有用
then consider checking out my inkscape
那就考虑看看我的Inkscape吧
master class it's a collection of over
大师类，它是一个集合
60 videos where I go over all of the
60个视频，我浏览了所有
tools and features in inkscape and I
Inkscape和I中的工具和功能
explain what they are and demonstrate
解释它们是什么并演示它们
how they work kind of like how I did in
它们的工作原理有点像我在
this video we even have a private
这个视频我们甚至有一个私人的
Community where you can ask questions
您可以提出问题的社区
and get help from me anytime you want
只要你愿意，随时向我寻求帮助
and best of all there's no monthly
最棒的是没有月刊
membership fees you just pay 17 one time
会员费你只需一次性付17英镑
and you're in for Life I'll have some
你要终身监禁，我要喝一些
information about that down below if you
如果您，请参阅下面的信息
want to check that out as always thanks
想一如既往地检查一下谢谢
for watching
收看
foreign
外国
[Music]
[音乐]